=Love For Two Lives=
= الحب لعمرين =
=Episode 6=
= الحلقة 6 =
Aunt.
عمة.
Let's do it before the King gets here.
لنفعل ذلك قبل وصول الملك إلى هنا.
Kill her as soon as possible.
اقتلها في أسرع وقت ممكن.
The time has come.
لقد حان الوقت.
Hang the witch.
شنق الساحرة.
Wait!
انتظر!
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I'm pregnant with the King's child.
أنا حامل بطفل الملك.
How dare you hang me?
كيف تجرؤ على شنقني؟
Don't listen to her nonsense.
لا تستمع إلى هرائها.
This witch can both climb and jump.
يمكن لهذه الساحرة التسلق والقفز.
And I caught her running around the palace yesterday.
ووجدتها وهي تركض في أرجاء القصر أمس.
It's impossible that she's pregnant.
من المستحيل أن تكون حامل.
Don't miss the right hour.
لا تفوت الساعة المناسبة.
Hang the witch.
شنق الساحرة.
You need the right time to hang me?
هل تحتاج الوقت المناسب لتشنقني؟
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
♪Get close to you♪
♪ اقترب منك
I said I'll protect you.
قلت سأحميك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I shouldn't have got you involved.
لا ينبغي أن أشركك.
I'll take you away now.
سآخذك بعيدا الآن.
King.
ملِك.
Are you going against the whole court for a witch?
هل أنت ضد المحكمة كلها لساحرة؟
Queen Mother.
الملكة الأم.
She's not a witch.
إنها ليست ساحرة.
Just let her go.
فقط دعها تذهب.
She's innocent.
إنها بريئة.
Don't, Aunt.
لا ، خالتي.
We don't know what will happen if we let her go.
لا نعرف ماذا سيحدث إذا تركناها تذهب.
That's right, Feier.
هذا صحيح يا فيير.
Guards.
حراس.
The King is enchanted by the witch.
الملك مفتون بالساحرة.
Kill the witch!
اقتل الساحرة!
Don't touch her!
لا تلمسها!
Get her!
احصل عليها!
Wait.
انتظر.
I'll tell you the truth.
سأقول لك الحقيقة.
I'm not a witch.
أنا لست ساحرة.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I'm a fairy.
أنا جنية.
Fairy?
جنية؟
Ridiculous.
سخيف.
This is ridiculous.
هذا سخيف.
I was roaming around here
كنت أتجول هنا
and foresaw
وتوقع
that the new Queen
أن الملكة الجديدة
of this country
من هذا البلد
would disappear for some reason.
ستختفي لسبب ما.
For the future of this Kingdom,
من أجل مستقبل هذه المملكة ،
I decided to stay and be the new Queen.
قررت أن أبقى وأن أكون الملكة الجديدة.
She's lying.
انها تكذب.
Aunt, you should kill her now.
عمتي ، يجب أن تقتلها الآن.
You...
أنت...
Her Majesty will never kill a fairy
صاحبة الجلالة لن تقتل جنية
just so you can be the Queen.
فقط لكي تكوني الملكة.
I won't
أنا لن
wrong anyone.
أي شخص خطأ.
As long as you can prove it.
طالما يمكنك إثبات ذلك.
I... I ran out of my power.
أنا ... نفدت قوتي.
Right.
الصحيح.
I need time to restore it.
أحتاج إلى وقت لاستعادته.
Don't let her go, Aunt.
لا تدعها تذهب يا عمة.
She'd run away.
كانت تهرب.
If she runs away, it only proves that she's a witch.
إذا هربت ، فهذا يثبت فقط أنها ساحرة.
She can never come back.
هي لا تستطيع العودة ابدا
Then,
ثم،
you'll still be the Queen.
ستظل الملكة.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll give you half an hour.
سأعطيك نصف ساعة.
This is the key.
هذا هو المفتاح.
Take it
خذها
and go.
و اذهب.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
I'll be back.
سأعود لاحقا.
Out of my way.
بعيدا عن طريقي.
Why is she leaving?
لماذا تغادر؟
Aunt, the incense is almost burned out.
عمة ، البخور تقريبا محترق.
The witch fled to escape punishment.
هربت الساحرة هربا من العقاب.
We'll choose a new Queen
سنختار ملكة جديدة
some other day.
في يوم آخر.
But,
ولكن،
where do we get a Queen now?
من أين نحصل على ملكة الآن؟
How about
ماذا عن
Princess Feier?
احتفال الاميرة؟
The Princess is virtuous,
الأميرة فاضلة ،
beautiful, and intelligent.
جميل وذكي.
Not to mention Her Highness is His Majesty's cousin.
ناهيك عن أن صاحبة السمو هي ابنة عم جلالة الملك.
I can't think of another person who suits the title better.
لا أستطيع التفكير في شخص آخر يناسب العنوان بشكل أفضل.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
They grew up together.
لقد نشأوا معًا.
A marriage within the clan.
زواج داخل العشيرة.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Aunt.
عمة.
I don't want to get married.
لا اريد الزواج.
I want to be with you forever.
أريد أن أكون معك للأبد.
This is the will of God.
هذه هي مشيئة الله.
Prepare for the wedding.
استعد لحفل الزفاف.
Yes.
نعم.
You mortals are too blind to recognize a real fairy.
أنتم بشر أعمى من أن تتعرفوا على جنية حقيقية.
She's a fairy?
هل هي جنية؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I'm here in the human world to save you.
أنا هنا في عالم البشر لإنقاذك.
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
♪Get close to you♪
♪ اقترب منك